You and me and a happy smiling shining happy train
Yeah, mega lucky super sparkly lucky train
Come on! Adventure's just around the corner
oh, my lucky tain!
You're Cinderella, and the clock's struck midnight
(too bad)
You want everyone to remember
(let's dance!)
Bid yourself from that night "goodbye"
Cuz tomorrow's back to normal
You're just an unpolished gem
you just have to keep polishing yourself
Countless hours passing by
Come on, it's your super shiny, ultra sparkly lucky time
Make a wish upon a shooting star before it passes you by
so you can once again board that ultra cheerful happy train
Maybe sometimes you'll slip up
but that might lead you to your treasure
Oh my happy train
Heart-pounding and thrilling -- oh my lucky train!